{
    "subject": "King_Vidor",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "His_Hour",
    "human_readable": "King Vidor created His Hour.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7017754316329956,
            "question": "Who created the film His Hour?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6632661819458008,
            "question": "When was His Hour likely created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41574087738990784,
            "question": "What is the title of the film King Vidor made?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34377530217170715,
            "question": "Is King Vidor known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31519654393196106,
            "question": "What genre might the film His Hour belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2848682403564453,
            "question": "Where might you find information about the film His Hour?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2816814184188843,
            "question": "What are some common themes in King Vidor's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2594107389450073,
            "question": "How influential was King Vidor in the history of cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24896733462810516,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors in King Vidor's films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2380136400461197,
            "question": "Can you name another film directed by King Vidor?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=King Vidor created His Hour.",
            "html": "yago_21673_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors in King Vidor's films?",
            "html": "yago_21673_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How influential was King Vidor in the history of cinema?",
            "html": "yago_21673_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes in King Vidor's work?",
            "html": "yago_21673_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21673_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21673_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21673_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21673_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21673_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21673_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21673_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21673_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21673_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21673_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not contain any information about King Vidor creating a film or production titled \"His Hour.\" The provided texts discuss his life, career as a director, and some of his notable films such as \"The Big Parade\" (1925), but there is no mention of \"His Hour.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}